Guide to the Marine Workers Historical Collection TAM.125
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- National Maritime Union: Wirtz, W. Willard v. National Maritime Union Transcripts (pages 854-928), Sep 26, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- National Maritime Union: Wirtz, W. Willard v. National Maritime Union Transcripts (pages 929-1008), Sep 26, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- National Maritime Union: Wirtz, W. Willard v. National Maritime Union Transcripts (pages 1009-1080), Sep 27, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- National Maritime Union: Wirtz, W. Willard v. National Maritime Union Transcripts (pages 1081-1176), Sep 27, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- National Maritime Union: Wirtz, W. Willard v. National Maritime Union Transcripts, Oct 27, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- National Maritime Union: Wirtz, W. Willard v. National Maritime Union Transcripts, Nov 29, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- National Union of Marine Cooks and Stewards: President Hugh Bryson and Secretary-Treasurer Eddie Tangen Memos, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Nickerson, William, et al.: Complaints about Captain Harris Signed by Union Members aboard Unidentified Ship (missing first page), undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
- "Pacific District Stewards News", Jan 19, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Padilla, Joseph: Rank and File Dissent Materials, 1956-1981 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Palazzi, Esther: Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Pendulick, Nicholas: Shipping Papers, 1943-1948 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Petersen, T. H.: Soup Kitchen Meal Ticket (Maritime Federation of the Pacific Strike) and King Ramsey Defense Fund Receipt, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Photographs of Tom Mooney, Loretta Szeliga, Joe Curran, Leona Robinson, Barney Lynch, Herman Deal, George Donohue, David Drummond (membership book and identification card), Jimmy Robbins, Danny Maltese, Duncan Keir, Moe Byne, 1930s-1980s (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Postcards of Ships (unsent), 1973, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Postek, Stanley (Ladislaus F. Szeliga): Arrests, 1934-1958 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Postek, Stanley: Clippings (Boxing), 1937-1945 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Postek, Stanley: Delegate Papers (National Maritime Union/CIO), 1943-1947 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Postek, Stanley: Expulsion of Postek and J. L. Jackson, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Postek, Stanley: Journal aboard the SS Oneida, 1939-1941 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Postek, Stanley: Membership Books, 1939-1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Postek, Stanley: Membership Standing, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Postek, Stanley: "My First Trip" Memoir (typescript), 1933 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Postek, Stanley: Security Appeal Hearing, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Postek, Stanley: Shipping Papers, 1936-1943 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Postek, Stanley: Strikes, 1937-1945 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Program for One National Union for Maritime Workers, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Ramos, David: "The Way it Was," National Maritime Union Pilot(Clipping), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Reed, Clarence: "One Three or More" by "A. Novice" (typescript), 1987 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Reed, Clarence: Oral History Transcript, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Research Resources in Maritime Labor History, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Robinson, Edward (Frenchy): Testimonial Dinner, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Rubin, Harry: "In the Case of Morrissey and Ibrahim v. Curran et al.," (pamphlet), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Sanjines, Carl: Correspondence with Marine Workers Historical Association, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Seamen's International Union Strike: "Draft of Compromise Suggested to Committee of Ship Owners", 1936 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Seamen's International Union Strike: Marine Cooks' and Stewards' Union, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Seamen's Defense Committee against Coast Guard Screening, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Scuttlebutt from the Waterfront (Vol. II, no. 1), Randall B. Smith, editor, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Ship Channel Progressive Committee: "Ship Channel," Newsletter (photocopies), 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Smith, Edwin Seymour: Obituaries, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Smith, Fredrick CA.: Proceedings of Testimonial Dinner in Honor of, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Sordes, George H.: National Maritime Union Card and Picket Cards, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Spanish Civil War: "How Franco Works, Part I," Clipping, National Maritime Union Pilot, Apr 1943 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Stack, Joseph: Trial Proceedings, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Stack, Joseph: "I Used to Cry When I Heard the Star Spangled Banner," Autobiography (typescript), undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Szeliga (Michel), Loretta: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Szeliga, Loretta: Memorabilia from Women's Auxiliary of the National Maritime Union, 1939-1946 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Taft, Philip: "Civil Rights in the National Maritime Union," Report (typescript), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Tank, Herbert: Communists on the Waterfront(pamphlet), 1946 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Tank, Herbert: Longitude 49, Book Cover and Photos, Posters, and Reviews of Play, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Tank, Herbert: National Maritime Union Identification and Financial Papers, 1942-1951 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- U.S. Merchant Marine Veterans (WWII): The Gangway(Vol. 2, No., 5-6; photocopies), 1985-1985 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Weiner, Morris: Account of Anti-Semitic Incident aboard the SS Pan Maryland, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Weiner, Morris: Charges against Traveler's Insurance, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Weiner, Morris: Complaint of Misconduct against Seymour Besunder, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Weiner, Morris: National Maritime Union Expulsion, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Weiner, Morris: Membership in Transport Workers Union Local 504, 1985-1991 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Weiner, Morris: Personal Papers, 1936-1986 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Weiner, Morris: Research on David Shapiro, 1949-1989 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Weiner, Morris: Signal Corps Radio Operators Manual and Q Signal Chart, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Women's Auxiliary of the National Maritime Union: First Anniversary Ball, Program, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Longitude 49 photographs, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Photos, negatives, poster, 1935-1983 (Box 4, Folder 48-54, Box Shared Tamiment 011, Folder 11)
- Filmstrip: Hiring Hall, Heart of the Union [Spanish}, 5 copies, 1948 (Box Shared Tamiment 004, Case 1)